http://www.groupbc.com/privacy

Post
I confirm that I have read and agree to your website terms of use, privacy policy and agree to the information I have entered 	above being used for marketing purposes.
Send
Download the Guide
First Name*
Last Name*
Company*
Email Address*
Phone*
How can we contact you now and in the future?*
Email
Phone
Post
I confirm that I have read and agree to your website terms of use, privacy policy and agree to the information I have entered 	above being used for marketing purposes.
Send
×
Search
Please enter your search terms below.
Search
All
Pages
Resources
Discover new opportunities with GroupBC
GroupBC are looking for partners who are passionate about delivering ongoing digital enhancements to their clients. Could you be one of our innovative digital partners?
Click here to sign up for our webinar and find out more
Solutions
Overview
Project Information Management
Asset Information Management
Our Products
BC Projects
BC Enterprise
Website Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Business Collaborator Ltd (trading as GroupBC) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the //www.groupbc.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to use of the Site. By agreeing for us to contact you by opting in to receive communication you are providing legal consent for such communication and the necessary processing and control of information to allow that communication to be provided.
1. Data Controller
Business Collaborator Ltd is the recipient and data controller of data collected from Users and we can be contacted direct during normal business hours on 0118 902 8543 or at our offices at 9th Floor, Reading Bridge House, Reading Bridge, Reading, Berkshire, RG1 8LS, United Kingdom.
Business Collaborator Ltd uses third party processors to deliver information via e-mail or via its Web Site. The processors are located in the USA and have provided evidence that their services meet the requirements of GDPR and will continue to do so.
If you have any complaint at all about our use of User’s data (as set out below) you have the right to ask us to remedy the situation. If you do not receive an adequate answer from us, then you can file a complaint with the relevant Data Protection Authority, which in the UK is the Information Commissioners Office. You can ask us to provide you with the information we hold about you and you can ask for that information to be corrected or removed. In order to achieve this please contact us using the information above or by using our contact form here.
2. Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users when they fill out an enquiry form or demonstration request form on the Site, subscribe to the newsletter from the Site, respond to a survey or make any similar online requests for assistance or support or register/log in to the support portal via the Site (or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site). Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, job title and company (if any) that they are representing. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect the above personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such personal identification information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
3. Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information. like most website, we use Google Analytics to help us to improve our website – details of the cookies this service uses can be found here.
4. Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
5. How we use collected information
Business Collaborator Ltd may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service – information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalise user experience – we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site – we may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature – to send Users information about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails – we may use a supplied email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If Users decide to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time Users would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or Users may contact us via our Site.
Users may revoke their consent at any time to our use of their personal identification information for the above purposes by using our contact form here.
6. How long will we hold your data
GroupBC will only hold your personal information securely for the period of time that it is actually needed to serve you relevant information about the products and services we supply.
7. Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. GroupBC does not carry out “profiling”.
8. Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
9. Changes to this privacy policy
Business Collaborator Ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
10. Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
11. Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us.
This privacy policy was last updated on October 17th, 2017.
Direct Marketing Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Business Collaborator Ltd (trading as GroupBC) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) as part of its direct marketing activity.
1. Direct Marketing Contact
GroupBC may contact you for the purposes of direct marketing. This means that GroupBC may use your personal data that it has collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy to contact you about events that you have registered for, products that you have purchased (or that have been purchased for you), reminders regarding any course you may be booked on or to tell you about GroupBC’s products. The direct marketing communications may be provided to you by social media channels, email, sms, post or phone or by any other reasonable means as GroupBC chooses.
Whenever we collect your personal data on our Websites, we will state whether we will use your personal data for direct marketing purposes. You will be provided with the opportunity to opt out of providing your consent to receiving these direct marketing communications both at the time that you provide your personal data and thereafter at any time by clicking on the relevant link or by using our contact form here. The GroupBC Website Privacy Policy is available here.
Whenever we collect your personal data through third party direct marketing companies and contact you, we will direct you to this policy whereby you will be provided with the opportunity to opt out of providing your consent to receiving these direct marketing communications. GroupBC only uses providers that have credentials that meet the requirements of GDPR. If you do not wish to be contacted in the future then please tell us when we contact you or use the options provided at the top of this policy or by using our contact form here.
Whenever we collect your personal data through our software, you will be provided with the ability to opt in and out of direct marketing contact. In addition, we will direct you to this policy whereby you will be provided with the opportunity to opt out of providing your consent. If you do not wish to be contacted in the future then please use the options provided at the top of this policy or by using our contact form here.
We may use your personal data to provide you with information about goods and services which we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (email or SMS) with information about goods or services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or discussions of a sale to you. If you are a new customer will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.
If you tell us that you do not want to receive any further direct marketing from us, we will not contact you further for the purpose of direct marketing. However, GroupBC will not necessarily remove your personal data from its database(s) if it considers it is fair and necessary to retain the personal data for another purpose.
2. Data Controller
Business Collaborator Ltd is the recipient and data controller of data collected from Users and we can be contacted direct during normal business hours on 0118 902 8543 or at our offices at 9th Floor, Reading Bridge House, Reading Bridge, Reading, Berkshire, RG1 8LS, United Kingdom.
Business Collaborator Ltd uses third party processors to deliver information via e-mail or via its Web Site. The processors are located in the USA and have provided evidence that their services meet the requirements of GDPR and will continue to do so.
If you have any complaint at all about our use of User’s data (as set out below) you have the right to ask us to remedy the situation. If you do not receive an adequate answer from us, then you can file a complaint with the relevant Data Protection Authority, which in the UK is the Information Commissioners Office. You can ask us to provide you with the information we hold about you and you can ask for that information to be corrected or removed. In order to achieve this please contact us using the information above or by using our contact form here.
3. Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users when they register for on-line or phone support or register their details in our software.
We may collect personal identification about Users from third party organisations.
Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, job title and company (if any) that they are representing. This information is voluntary and can be removed.
4. Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our software. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to the software. We do not carry out any analytics on this information other than that required to ensure cyber security.
5. How we use collected information
Business Collaborator Ltd uses Users’ personal identification information for the following purposes only:
To improve customer service – information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalise user experience – we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Web Site – we may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or to send Users information about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails – we may use a supplied email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If Users’ decide to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time Users would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or Users may contact us via our Web Site.
To provide the necessary contact information for Support requests
To provide information relating to maintenance of Cyber Security
Users may revoke their consent at any time to our use of their personal identification information for the above purposes by by using our contact form here.
6. How long will we hold your data
GroupBC will only hold your personal information securely for the period of time that it is actually needed to serve you relevant information about the products and services we supply.
7. Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. GroupBC does not carry out “profiling”.
8. How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
9. Changes to this privacy policy
Business Collaborator Ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
10. Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us.
This privacy policy was last updated on January 24th, 2018.
Click here to book a demo today and find out how our BC solutions
can help you improve your digital construction and asset delivery
Learn More
